If you only have 24 hours in a day,
your success will depend on
how you manage the 24 hours.
You should listen to me.
People are talking about Oprah Winfrey,
Ted Turner, and Warren Buffett.
Listen to me,
I don't care how much money you make,
you only have 24 hours a day
and the difference between Oprah and a broke person
is that Oprah uses her time wisely.
Listen to me, this is why
focus well, you
have 24 hours.
I don't care if you're broke, or were born poor.  .
I don't care if you were born rich, and
I don't care if you were in university, or
you only have 24 hours.
For this reason, I earned money from every side,
from being a high school dropout
to selling 6,000 books in less than 6 months.
What happened to the 24 hours in my day?
I was saying to myself: Well, Eric, you
need to take control of your time
because you're about to be broke for the rest of your life.
And this is what I would like you to do.
I can tell you about your entire life.
If you write down your daily schedule for me,
let me see it.
I will tell you what you will be in 5 years. I will tell
you where you will be in 10 years.
I will tell you where you will be in 20 years if you continue with the same daily schedule.
Translated by: Fatima Al-Dufyan,